{
    "subject": "resource/Nick_Greiner",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1947-04-27",
    "human_readable": "Nick Greiner was born on April 27, 1947.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9663769602775574,
            "question": "Nick Greiner's birthdate is April 27th, what year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8957079648971558,
            "question": "When was Nick Greiner born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8822661638259888,
            "question": "Who was born on April 27, 1947?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8514102697372437,
            "question": "Is April 27th a significant date in Nick Greiner's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.756926417350769,
            "question": "What is Nick Greiner's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6915243268013,
            "question": "What day of the month was Nick Greiner born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6825041770935059,
            "question": "What month and day was Nick Greiner born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46897372603416443,
            "question": "In what year did Nick Greiner come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42729493975639343,
            "question": "On what date did Nick Greiner enter the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32067054510116577,
            "question": "April 27th holds significance for whom?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nick Greiner was born on April 27, 1947.",
            "html": "dbpedia_615_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=On what date did Nick Greiner enter the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_615_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Nick Greiner come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_615_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What month and day was Nick Greiner born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_615_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_615_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_615_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_615_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_615_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_615_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_615_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_615_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_615_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_615_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_615_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the information in the documents confirms that Nick Greiner was indeed born on April 27, 1947."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents consistently state that Nick Greiner was born on April 27, 1947. This information is present in multiple files (51.txt and 8.txt), confirming the accuracy of the statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}